<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<root>
    <ARTIST ID="1">
        <NAME>Ardo Liltamor</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Es un grupo de danza dedicado al estudio, investigación, puesta en escena y difusión de las danzas del Renacimiento europeo. Dirigido por la profesora Cecilia Nadaszkiewicz desde su creación en el año 2004 y de manera ininterrumpida, Ardo Liltamor tiene participación activa en encuentros relacionados con la literatura fantástica, la recreación histórica, exposiciones de arte, eventos culturales en general donde la música y la danza ponen de manifiesto la alegría de la creación artística.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>A dance company dedicated to the study, research, staging and promotion of European Renaissance dances. With professor Cecilia Nadaszkiewicz serving as its director since its creation in 2004, Ardo Liltamor has an active participation in events related to fantastic literature, historical reenactment, art exhibitions and cultural events in general where music and dance manifest the joy of artistic creation.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f301dff7614c_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:37:51</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:37:51</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="2">
        <NAME>Beltaine. Música Medieval</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Formado a fines de 2008, Beltaine surge del elenco del musical El Caballero enDuendado. Integrado por Maru Aponte (voz, bodhrán, low whistle), Julia Faletty (bodhrán, cajón, derbake y accesorios), Gachi Flores (tin whistles, flautas dulces, flauta travesera irlandesa) y Santiago Pérez de Muro (guitarra).</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Formed in late 2008, Beltaine emerges from the cast of the musical El Caballero enDuendado. The band is made up of Maru Aponte (vocals, bodhrán, low whistle), Julia Faletty (bodhrán, cajón, darbuka and accessories), Gachi Flores (tin whistles, recorders, Irish flute) and Santiago Pérez de Muro (guitar).</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f301f48bd6ed_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:43:20</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:43:20</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="3">
        <NAME>TSO (Teatro Sanitario de Operaciones)</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Es un proceso artístico. Se inició en 1996 y adaptó sus obras a los tiempos actuales. Es dialéctico, no se encuadra en un dogma, no tiene moral a la hora de elegir los elementos para trabajar. El método es creativo colectivo. Usa el cotidianismo descontextualizado en relatos ficticios pero fácilmente enmarcados en la realidad. Utiliza, en lugares no convencionales, el cruce de lenguajes: video, teatro, poesía y teatro aéreo.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>TSO (Teatro Sanitario de Operaciones) is an artistic process. Created in 1996, the group has adapted its plays to present times. They have a dialectic, dogma-free approach, and they are not limited by any doctrine when choosing their working materials. The method used is creative and collective. The group takes everyday life situations out of context and apply them into their fictional plots. They perform in unconventional spaces combining the languages of video, theater, poetry and aerial theater.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f301f9f81ee0_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:44:47</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:44:47</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="4">
        <NAME>Gustavo Garabito</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Oriundo de Temperley, provincia de Buenos Aires, entra en el mundo del teatro de títeres en 1998. Se desempeña como titiritero y también como realizador. Cursa en la Escuela Municipal de Titiriteros de Avellaneda (2004, 2005); en la Escuela Taller de Libertablas (2007) y en la Escuela de Titiriteros del Teatro San Martín, Ariel Bufano (2008, 2010). Es integrante y fundador del grupo La Naranja Retáblica, con el que realiza espectáculos, performances y varieté junto a Fernando Amarilla, desde 2003 hasta la actualidad.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Gustavo Garabito, born in Temperley, province of Buenos Aires, took his first steps into the world of puppet theater in 1998. Currently, he is a puppeteer and also a puppet maker. He studied puppetry at Escuela Municipal de Titiriteros de Avellaneda (2004, 2005), Escuela Taller de Libertablas (2007) and Escuela de Titiriteros del Teatro San Martín, Ariel Bufano (2008, 2010). He is a founding member of La Naranja Retáblica theater group, with which he has been staging theater productions, performances and variety shows together with Fernando Amarilla since 2003.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f301fca1c323_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:45:30</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:45:30</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="5">
        <NAME>Carlos Rivas</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Carlos Rivas es director de teatro y televisión graduado en la Escuela Nacional de Arte Dramático (Argentina). Se formó como director con Carlos Gandolfo y Augusto Fernandes, además de estudiar escenografía con Saulo Benavente. Se ha desempeñado como profesor de actuación y dramaturgo. Dirigió más de veinte obras; entre ellas La prueba y La duda por las que obtuvo los premios ACE, Clarín y Estrella de Mar. Actualmente dirige Hamlet, la metamorfosis.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Carlos Rivas is a theater and television director, graduated from the National School of Dramatic Arts (Argentina). He received directing training from Carlos Gandolfo and Augusto Fernandes, in addition to studying set design with Saulo Benavente. He has worked as an acting teacher and playwright. He has directed over twenty plays, notably La prueba and La duda for which he received the ACE, Clarín and Estrella de Mar awards. He currently directs Hamlet, la metamorfosis.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3020ae6e50b_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:49:18</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:49:18</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="6">
        <NAME>Ximena Belgrano Rawson</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Formada en el Teatro Colón, ha dirigido ópera y teatro. Se destacan el estreno mundial de ¡Oh, el amor, el amor!, de Valdo Sciammarella para el Teatro Colón e Historia de un proceso en el marco del Primer Ciclo Nacional de Ópera Contemporánea. Por medio de la beca Edesal, The Capital Experience trabajó para la Source Theatre Company de Washington D.C.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Educated at the Colon Theater, she has directed several opera and theater productions, notably the world premiere of Valdo Sciammarella's ¡Oh, el amor, el amor!, for the Colon Theater, and Historia de un proceso, within the framework of the First National Series of Contemporary Opera. As a scholarship recipient of Edesal - The Capital Experience program, she worked for the Source Theatre Company, in Washington D.C.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f328cca9b381_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 18:37:06</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-08 14:55:06</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="7">
        <NAME>Filarmonica Clown</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>112</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>La Filarmonica Clown es un trío formado por Carlo Rossi (conocido por muchos niños por el personaje de Empirio del programa de la RAI, El Árbol Azul), Piero Lenardon y Valerio Bongiorno. Esta compañía nace en 1978. Desde sus comienzos, su trabajo da testimonio de una original observación del humorismo cotidiano y una elaboración personal del lenguaje del clown.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>The Filarmonica Clown is a trio made up of Carlo Rossi (well-known among children for playing Empirio on RAI's television show El Árbol Azul), Piero Lenardon and Valerio Bongiorno. This company was born in 1978, and since then, their artistic output reflects an original take on everyday humor and their own brand of clown theater.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3281e8ed6de_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:05:59</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-08 14:08:40</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="8">
        <NAME>Sergio Amigo</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Sergio Amigo es director y docente de teatro. Está radicado en Londres desde el año 2000. En 1994 funda en Buenos Aires La Cabeza del Jabalí, compañía argentina dedicada a Shakespeare. En Sídney (Australia) monta Fever: A Latin-Australian Shakespeare Experience. Ya radicado en Londres, recorre, con Los Sonetos, Turquía, España, Inglaterra e India. Actualmente es el director artístico de su propio espacio, The Calder Bookshop and Theatre. Enseña Acting Shakespeare en el Morley College y en la prisión de Wandsworth.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Sergio Amigo is a theater director and teacher. He has been living in London since 2000. In 1994 in Buenos Aires, he founded La Cabeza del Jabalí, an Argentine theater company dedicated to Shakespeare. In Sidney (Australia), he staged Fever: A Latin-Australian Shakespeare Experience. Once based in London, he toured with Los Sonetos to Turkey, Spain, England and India. He is the founder and artistic director of The Calder Bookshop and Theatre. He teaches an Acting Shakespeare course at Morley College and at Wandsworth Prison.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3024b3e9d25_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:06:27</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:06:27</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="9">
        <NAME>Patricio Orozco</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Patricio Orozco es director teatral y creador de los festivales Beckett de Buenos Aires y Shakespeare de Buenos Aires. Ha obtenido menciones de los Premios Teatro del Mundo y María Guerrero. Actualmente es el director artístico del II Festival Buenos Aires Shakespeare.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Patricio Orozco is a theater director and the creator of the Beckett and the Shakespeare Buenos Aires festivals. He has been awarded at the Teatro del Mundo and María Guerrero Awards.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3024fb4a8ca_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:07:39</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:07:39</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="10">
        <NAME>Quique López</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Dirige el TSO, que se inició en 1996 con un método creativo colectivo. Utiliza el cruce de lenguajes (videoarte, teatro aéreo, poesía) sin escenarios y en lugares no convencionales.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>The TSO, directed by Quique López, started in 1996 following a collective and creative method. Performances use a combination of languages (video art, aerial theater, poetry) and are staged in unconventional places.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3025b322705_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:10:43</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:10:43</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="11">
        <NAME>Marcelo Savignone</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Marcelo Savignone es actor, director y docente teatral. Fundador de la Compañía Sucesos Argentinos y alma de Belisario Club de Cultura. Algunas de sus producciones teatrales han sido HxH, Hamlet por Hamlet, Vivo, Suerte, El vuelo, Felis, Brazos quiebran, En sincro, Cinemascope, Comeclavos, Mojiganga, una pieza irrepetible o La esperata.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Marcelo Savignone is an actor, director and theater teacher. He is the founder of the Compañía Sucesos Argentinos and a key figure of the Belisario Club de Cultura. Some of his stage productions include HxH, Hamlet por Hamlet, Vivo, Suerte, El vuelo, Felis, Brazos quiebran, En sincro, Cinemascope, Comeclavos, Mojiganga, una pieza irrepetible and La esperata.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3025d451a1c_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:11:16</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:11:16</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="12">
        <NAME>Malena Solda, Daniel Suárez Marzal y Miguel de Olaso</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Trabajaron juntos en la puesta de La Celestina para el Teatro San Martín, en 2008. Siguieron investigando el Siglo de Oro español y el teatro isabelino hasta llegar a darle forma a este nuevo espectáculo. Víctor Torres se suma a este proyecto tras la necesidad de incorporar a un reconocido intérprete de música de cámara, ópera y oratorio.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Malena Solda, Daniel Suárez Marzal and Miguel de Olaso worked together in the staging of La Celestina for the Teatro San Martín in 2008. Afterwards, they dedicated to the study of the Spanish Golden Age and Elizabethan theater until this new stage production came into being. Víctor Torres joined the project as they needed a renowned performer of chamber music, opera and oratorio.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3026955aab3_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:14:29</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:14:29</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="13">
        <NAME>Los Carlinga y La Pomponio</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Los Carlinga y La Pomponio está formada por tres actores: Fabián Carrasco, Nicolás Goldschmidt y Marta Pomponio. Este trío se inició en las clases de Ricardo Bartís en el Sportivo Teatral y surgió a partir de la lectura de las obras más emblemáticas de Shakespeare. Alberto y Hugo Carlinga (Los Hermanos Carlinga) y Estela Pomponio son los intérpretes que también nos contarán su propia historia.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Los Carlinga y La Pomponio is made up of three actors: Fabián Carrasco, Nicolás Goldschmidt and Marta Pomponio. This trio met in the classes taught by Ricardo Bartís at the Sportivo Teatral and emerged from the reading of Shakespeare's most emblematic works. Alberto and Hugo Carlinga (Los Hermanos Carlinga) and Estela Pomponio are the musical performers, who will also tell us their own story.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3029285918e_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:25:28</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:25:28</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="14">
        <NAME>Los Modernos</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Sólo dos actores: Pedro Paiva y Alejandro Orlando. Son una especie de Les Luthiers minimalistas, sin instrumentos, sin fama, casi sin recorrido. Utilizan un lenguaje teatral con código propio. Son un fenómeno que apela a la palabra y nada más que a la palabra, para armar un espectáculo no solo divertido sino, extremadamente lúcido. Los Modernos, un misterio para ser develado… viéndolo.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Only two actors: Pedro Paiva and Alejandro Orlando. They are a sort of minimalist version of Les Luthiers, without instruments, without renown, almost without experience. They use their own brand of theatrical language. They are a phenomenon that resorts to words and nothing but words to put up a show that is not only funny but also extremely clever. Los Modernos – a mystery to be unraveled...by the viewer.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f302647a5527_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:13:11</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 19:13:11</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="15">
        <NAME>Stanley E. Gontarski</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>75</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Profesor Distinguido de Literatura Inglesa (premio Robert O. Lawton), doctorado en la Universidad de Ohio State (1974), Gontarzki se especializa en estudios sobre literatura irlandesa del siglo XX, en modernismo británico, norteamericano y europeo, y en teoría de la actuación. Ha recibido cuatro becas de investigación de la National Endowment for the Humanities y dos becas Fulbright de intercambio para docentes universitarios. Trabajó como editor invitado para las siguientes publicaciones: American Book Review, The Review of Contemporary Fiction y Modern Fiction Studies, y más recientemente, para Drammaturgia. De 1989 a 2008, se desempeñó como editor del Journal of Beckett Studies, publicación de la Edinburgh University Press, donde actualmente es coeditor.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Robert O. Lawton Distinguished Professor of English, Ph.D., Ohio State (1974): specializes in twentieth-century Irish Studies, in British, U.S., and European Modernism, and in performance theory. He has been awarded four National Endowment for the Humanities research grants, has twice been awarded Fulbright Professorships. He has been Guest Editor of the following: American Book Review, The Review of Contemporary Fiction and Modern Fiction Studies, and most recently Drammaturgia. He edited the Journal of Beckett Studies from 1989 to 2008, and currently serves as Co-Editor with its publication by Edinburgh University Press.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f304058d6e86_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:04:24</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:04:24</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="16">
        <NAME>Penny Cherns</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Es actriz, directora y docente. Nacida en Inglaterra, ha trabajado en la BBC y el Channel 4 en gran cantidad de series. En el West-End londinense trabajó en las obras Kiss Me Kate, Chicago, The Odd Couple y A Doll’s House. Como docente, se ha desempeñado en la London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art, Royal Academy of Dramatic Art, Bristol University, entre otras. Ha brindado seminarios relacionados con la obra de William Shakespeare en las ciudades de Londres, Ámsterdam, Oslo, Iowa, Nueva York, San Pablo y Montevideo.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>She is an actress, director and teacher. Born in England, she has worked for the BBC and Channel 4 in a great number of shows. In London’s West End, she appeared on productions such as Kiss Me Kate, Chicago, The Odd Couple and A Doll’s House. As a teacher, she has served on the faculties of the London Academy of Music and Dramatic Art, the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art, Bristol University, among others. She has delivered Shakespeare seminars in the cities of London, Amsterdam, Oslo, Iowa, New York, Sao Paulo and Montevideo.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f304078ca23e_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:04:56</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:04:56</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="17">
        <NAME>Daniel Kelly</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>180</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Daniel Kelly nació en Reino Unido. Es actor y ha trabajado en The Merry Wives of Windsor, Macbeth, A Lover’s Complaint y The Rape of Lucrece.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Daniel Kelly was born in the United Kingdom. He is an actor and has performed in The Merry Wives of Windsor, Macbeth, A Lover’s Complaint and The Rape of Lucrece.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f30410670b5b_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:06:26</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:07:18</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="18">
        <NAME>Mónica Maffia</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Estudió música y teatro en Londres. Se graduó como Bachelor of Arts (Honours), por la Middlesex University. Realizó el doctorado en la USAL. Este año defenderá su tesis doctoral sobre Shakespeare. Es fundadora y directora del Grupo de Teatro FyL (Filosofía y Letras, UBA); es también régisseuse egresada del Instituto Superior de Arte del Teatro Colón. Obtuvo el Premio Mayor Teatro del Mundo (UBA) por su traducción de Eduardo III, de Shakespeare, la primera para América Latina, publicada por Ediciones Corregidor.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>She studied music and theater in London. She graduated as a Bachelor of Arts (Honors) from the Middlesex University. She completed a postgraduate course at the USAL. This year, she will defend her doctoral thesis on Shakespeare. She is founder and director of Grupo de Teatro FyL (School of Philosophy and Letters, UBA); she is also a régisseuse, graduated from the Instituto Superior de Arte of the Colón Theater. She received the award Premio Mayor Teatro del Mundo (UBA) for her translation of Shakespeare's Edward III, the first one for Latin America, published by Ediciones Corregidor.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3041783df02_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:09:12</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:09:12</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>

    <ARTIST ID="19">
        <NAME>Laura Silva</NAME>
        <ID_COUNTRY>13</ID_COUNTRY>
        <BIO_ES>Laura Silva es directora, actriz y dramaturga. Egresó de la carrera de Dirección Teatral de la ENAD y se formó sobre la estética del Teatro de Imagen con Alberto Félix Alberto. Colabora con The Cambridge World Shakespeare Encyclopedia para su edición 2012 y es miembro de la International Shakespeare Association (Reino Unido). Ha sido invitada como expositora al 9th World Shakespeare Congress (Praga, 2011). Actualmente es Directora Artística del Teatro El Cubo.</BIO_ES>
        <BIO_EN>Laura Silva is director, actress and playwright. She majored in Theater Direction at the ENAD and studied the aesthetics of Image Theater with Alberto Félix Alberto. She collaborates with The Cambridge World Shakespeare Encyclopedia for its 2012 edition and is a member of the International Shakespeare Association (United Kingdom). She was invited as speaker at the 9th World Shakespeare Congress (Prague, 2011). She is currently the Artistic Director of the Teatro El Cubo.</BIO_EN>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_ES>Información Extra</EXTRA_TITLE_ES>
        <EXTRA_TITLE_EN>Extra Information</EXTRA_TITLE_EN>
        <FILEPIC1>4f3041a84ff8e_1</FILEPIC1>
        <ID_YOUTUBE></ID_YOUTUBE>
        <PUBLISHED>1</PUBLISHED>
        <CREATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:10:00</CREATED_TS>
        <UPDATED_TS>2012-02-06 21:10:00</UPDATED_TS>
    </ARTIST>
</root>
